https://www.replacementremotes.com/privacy_policy

Home
Privacy Policy
COMPARE
REPLACEMENTREMOTES.COM'S PRIVACY POLICY
Dan's Electronics Etc., Inc. DBA Replacement Remotes (RR) and Anderic® is committed to respecting and protecting your privacy. To that end, we have prepared this privacy statement to disclose and describe our information gathering and dissemination practices for this website.
Notice and Disclosure
In general, you may visit this website without identifying yourself or revealing any personal information. RR collects domain information from your visit to customize and improve your experience on our website. Some portions of this website may require you to give us personally identifiable information, which is information that enables us to identify you, such as your name, email or other address. If you opt to provide us that sort of information, we also may use it for purposes such as verifying your identity, sending you information or contacting you. For certain programs, we may make your information available to our partners, for marketing and other purposes which we believe may be beneficial to you.
Choice/Opt-Out
It is our intent to inform you before we collect personally identifiable information, and tell you what we intend to do with it. You will have the option of not providing the information, in which case you may still be able to access other portions of this website, although you may not be able to access certain services or areas. In certain portions of this website, we also may enable you to "opt out" of certain uses of your information, or elect not to receive future communications or services. This is entirely your choice.
Data Security
RR's intent is to strictly protect the security of your personal information; honor your choice for its intended use; and carefully protect your data from loss, misuse, unauthorized access or disclosure, alteration, or destruction. We have put in place appropriate physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure information we collect online.
Business Relationships
This website contains links to other websites. RR is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites.
Cookies
Portions of this website use cookies to keep track of your visit, or to deliver content specific to your interests. A "Cookie" is a small amount of data transferred to your browser and read by the Web server that placed it there. It works as a sort of identification card, recording your preferences and previously entered information. You can set your browser to notify you when you receive a cookie, giving you the chance to accept or reject it.
Contacting Us
If you have any questions or comments about our privacy statement or practices, please contact us via email with the words PRIVACY POLICY written in the subject line.
Replacement Remotes reserves the right to modify or update this privacy statement at any time without notice.
FREE SHIPPING ON ORDERS $50+ (USA)!
1-855-573-6683 | Support | Sign In | Cart: 0 items
FREE SHIPPING ON ORDERS $50+ (USA)!
Brands
ANDERICAnderic GenericsBOSECOMCASTCobyContinu.usDENONDish-NetworkDynexEMERSONETECElementFUNAIGenericHISENSEHITACHIHaierHampton-BayINSIGNIAJBLJVCKENWOODLGLiftmasterLogitechMARANTZMagnavoxONKYOPHILIPSPIONEERPanasonicPolaroidProscanRCAROKUSAMSUNGSANYOSEIKISHARPSONYSceptreTCLTOSHIBAVIOREVIZIOWestinghouseYAMAHAZENITHZvoxxfinity
VIEW ALL BRANDS
Categories
3D GlassesAccessoriesCablesFlash DrivesAir Conditioner UnitsAmplifiersAudio SystemsAudio/Video ReceiversBlu-Ray & Home Theater SystemsBlu-Ray DVD PlayersBookshelf Audio SystemsCable BoxesCamcordersCeiling Fan KitsCeiling Fan ReceiversCommercial TVsDVD PlayersHome Theater SystemsJackpacksLCD ProjectorsLight BulbsMonitorsOperating ManualsPartsAC Power CordsBatteriesBattery CoversIR Receiver ModulesPower SuppliesRemote DonglesProjectorsProjector LampsRefrigerator Water FiltersRemote ControlsGarage Door OpenersRemote Control TestersRemote Wall Mount ClipsSatellite ReceiversSecurity CablesSound Bar SystemsTunersTVsTV StandsTV/DVD CombosWall MountsWireless HD Video/Audio converters
VIEW ALL CATEGORIES
Most Popular
Recently Added
Advanced Search
Why Buy Here?
Customer ReviewsShipping InformationWarranty/Guarantee InformationUser AgreementPrivacy PolicyReturn-Cancellation PolicyProjector Lamps Warranty
Other Services
BlogYouTube ChannelHave remotes to sell? We buy them!AffiliatesRecycle
Help Links
Hospitality RemotesFAQHow to Test My Remote ControlSite MapContact UsAbout Our CompanyAnderic Official WebsiteAnderic RRU401 Code Lookup Tool
Newsletter Signup
Special offers, extra departures and news
Copyright ©2020 ReplacementRemotes.com.
All Rights ReservedWeb Programming: CF-Works
Sign In
Cart:
